Yahor Paulovich

CREATIVITY • PERFORMANCE • SELF-DEVELOPMENT • COMMUNICABILITY • TRAINABILITY



Unity Developer

Game Developer

 $\circ \circ \circ$



SUMMARY

I am focused on creating maintainable and scalable solutions that meet the needs of OOP and SOLID principles & business goals.

I specialize in writing clean code architecture using DI, applying design patterns, and implementing various gameplay mechanics.

I love to solve complicated problems in a simple and beautiful way and by giving a problem to me you can be sure I found a creative solution for it!

PORTFOLIO



https://github.com/YahorPaulovich/Portfolio



https://github.com/YahorPaulovich



https://yahor-paulovich.itch.io







CONTACTS

+48 728 377 407



yahorpaulovich

@Yahor_Paulovich

live:.cid.c78181f6e842ded6

Pogodna Bialystok, 15-354, Poland

LANGUAGES

EN B1+ BY Native ы

UA

RU

I have no problem reading technical documentation, but I still need to improve my English



EXPERIENCE



Unity Developer Jan 2024 - Present · 3 mos

Hype Games FZE LLC · Part-time Dubai, United Arab Emirates · Remote

Prototyping Action and Casual games.

Skills: C# · Unity · Zenject · WebGL.



Middle Unity Developer Feb 2024 - Mar 2024 · 2 mos

Voidverse Studios · Full-time

Toronto, Ontario, Canada · Remote **Skills:** C# \cdot Unity \cdot Zenject \cdot Mobile Application Development.



Unity Developer Oct 2023 - Present · 4 mos

Extension Forces · Part-time

Buenos Aires, Argentina · Remote

Simulator game development and Xreal Light MR/VR/AR prototyping in an outsourcing company.

Skills: C# · Unity · Virtual Reality (VR) · Augmented Reality (AR) · Mixed Reality (MR) · Zenject.



Unity Developer May 2023 - Dec 2023 · 8 mos

Freelance

Remote

Prototyping Action, Adventure and NDA Indies games development for clients on Upwork and Facebook.

 $\textbf{Skills:} \ \texttt{C\#} \cdot \texttt{Unity} \cdot \texttt{Zenject} \cdot \texttt{Hyper Casual Game Development} \cdot \texttt{ML-Agents}.$



(Principal) Unity Developer Jul 2023 - Sep 2023 · 3 mos

ARROWS · unpaid startup

Almaty, Kazakhstan · Remote

I focus on programming game mechanics and ooptimize performance, debug issues, and implement new features. I collaborate with 2D and 3D artists and UI/UX designers in my team.

Skills: URP Custom Renderer Features · Multithreaded Programming · DOTS · Animation Rigging · Gameplay Programming · Software Development · C# · Unity.



Unity Developer Jan 2023 - Apr 2023 · 4 mos

Gamedev Camp · Seasonal

Vilniaus, Lithuania · Remote

Online mentorship program for game developers with a focus on talent from Ukraine, Lithuania, Poland and around. I won a grant to participate in the second season.

 $\textbf{Skills:} \ \texttt{C\#} \cdot \texttt{Unity} \cdot \texttt{Unity's Data-Oriented Technology Stack} \cdot \texttt{Gameplay Programming} \cdot \texttt{Software}$ Development · Communication · English.



Unity Developer Jul 2021 - Jul 2022 · 1 yr 1 mo

Gammister · Full-time

Dubai, United Arab Emirates · Remote

Developing the NDA gambling project from scratch to a finished prototype and to beta testing on the Google Play Store.

The project was quite complex and innovative, I learned a lot.

Skills: C# · Unity · ASP.NET Core SignalR · ASP.NET Entity Framework Core · Microsoft SQL Server · Docker · Ubuntu Server 20.04 LTS · Git · Postman · Android · Mobile Application Development · Problem Solving · Software Design Patterns · OOP.

HARD SKILLS

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: C#
Game Engine: Unity

Platforms: Android, PC, WebGL and Pico VR

VCS

Git

NETWORKING

Mirror Networking

NON-RDBMS

Firebase Database

ARCHITECTURAL SKILLS

In OOP style, I can design Clean, Onion, Hexagonal and Data Driven Architecture

PACKAGES

UI, Tilemap, Animations, Timeline, Animation Rigging, Cinemachine, Physics, New Input System, Al Navigation, Audio, Localization, Addressables, URP Renderer Features, Shader Graph, Visual Effect Graph, Particle System, IAP,

PLUGINS

DOTween, Google Play Games, A* Pathfinding Project Pro, Agents Navigation, Amplify Shader Editor, FMOD for Unity

SDKs

PicoVR Unity SDK, GameAnalytics, AppsFlyer, OneSignal SDK

LIBRARIES

Zenject, UniTask, Newtonsoft.Json

DATA-ORIENTED TECHNOLOGY STACK

ECS for Unity, Burst Compiler, C# Job System

OTHER SKILLS

LANGUAGES

C++, Java

ORM

Microsoft ASP.NET Entity Framework Core

RDBMS

Microsoft SQL Server, MySQL, MariaDB

NETWORKING

Protocols: TCP, UDP, WebSockets, WebRTC
Libraries: Microsoft ASP.NET Core SignalR
Server OS: Ubuntu Linux Server, Windows Server

PAAS: Docker

Cloud Platforms: Microsoft Azure, Digital Ocean, Google Cloud Platform

EDUCATION

Bachelor's Degree in Software Engineering and Economics

International University MITSO 2018 - 2022

Information Systems and Technologies (In Economics) GPA: 3.8

The main disciplines studied were: Web design and design patterns; System analysis and design of information systems (with a web application development module); Scripting programming languages; Computer networks; Applied data processing systems; Algorithmization and programming; Programming network applications; Object-oriented design and programming; Distributed information systems; Probability theory and mathematical statistics; Software development technologies;

 $\begin{tabular}{ll} \textbf{Skills:} Software Engineering} \cdot Software Development} \cdot Mobile Applications \cdot C\# \cdot .NET Core \cdot C++ \\ \cdot \cdot \cdot \cdot OOP \cdot Software Design Patterns \cdot Microsoft SQL Server \cdot Transact-SQL (T-SQL) \cdot Microsoft Foundation Class (MFC) \cdot Android Studio \cdot JavaSE \cdot JavaServer Pages (JSP) \cdot MySQL \cdot Java Database Connectivity (JDBC) \cdot Java Swing \cdot HTML5 \cdot Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) \cdot JavaScript \cdot TypeScript \cdot NumPy \cdot Pandas \cdot Node.js \cdot Express.js \\ \end{tabular}$

... BOOKSHELF













